http://www.pmpa.org/utility-pages/privacy-policy

Like PMPA on Facebook
Join the conversation with PMPA on Twitter Add PMPA to a circle on Google+ Join PMPA's network on LinkedIn Watch PMPA's videos on YouTube View PMPA's photos on Flickr Subscribe to PMPA via RSS
About PMPA
Contact Us
Membership
How You Will BenefitMembership Types, Dues, Join
Events
ScheduleNational Events
Update Conference (Early Spring)National Technical Conference (Late Spring)Annual Meeting (Fall)Mastery Program (One Year Program)Precision Machining Technology Show (PMTS)
Local EventsOnline Events
Technical Tuesday WebinarsPodcastsBlogPMPA Online Town Halls
News
Latest News
For Members
Blog
Knowledge & ToolsCareersListServes
Home/ Privacy Policy
My Profile
Privacy Policy
Email Lists
Print
Privacy Policy
Cookies Cookies are small data files that websites can write to your hard drive when you visit them. Once written, the cookie can only be accessed by the site that originally created it (ie. our site cannot read cookies set by another site you have visited and vice-versa). Our site uses cookies to store personal site preferences, session information, and ordering information specific to you (such as the contents of your shopping cart).
External Site Links This site contains links to other websites on the internet. While we provide links to them, we are not responsible for their content or privacy policies.
IP Addresses and Logging Our server logs information regarding visitors to our site, such as IP address, date/time, and pages accessed. This information is used to generate reports for statistical purposes.
Buyer Information Information, such as names and email addresses, are collected from buyers at the time of a sale in order to complete the purchase. This information is NOT sold or distributed to third parties. We are firmly against spam and neither participate nor promote any activities that assist spammers.
Order Processing PayPal.com is a payment gateways that PMPA uses.  All credit card transactions are securely processed. The information collected PayPal.com payment forms are not recorded by PMPA.
Changes to this Privacy Policy We may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
Questions or Suggestions If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact us.
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Precision Machined Products Association. All rights reserved.
Precision Machined Products Association 6880 West Snowville Road, Suite 200, Brecksville, OH 44141
p: (440) 526-0300
|
f: (440) 526-5803
Association web design and development by Matrix Group International, Inc.
Our Partners
